sigmaassessmentsystems.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | SIGMA Assessment Systems

### Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the SIGMAAssessmentSystems.Com website. This website has agreed to notify you of:

  * what personally identifiable information about you or any third party is collected from you through the website;
  * the organization collecting the information;
  * how the information is used;
  * with whom the information may be shared;
  * what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
  * the kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under SIGMA Assessment Systems’ control;
  * how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact the Privacy Coordinator [by email](http://www.sigmaassessmentsystems.com/contact/ "Contact"), or by postal mail at **SIGMA Assessment Systems, P.O. Box 610757, Port Huron, Michigan, USA 48061-0757** or  **Research Psychologists Press, P.O. Box 3292, Station B, London, Ontario, Canada N6A 4K3**.

## Information Collection and Use

SIGMA Assessment Systems is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. SIGMA Assessment Systems collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

## Order

We request information from the customer on our order form. There, our customers must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this information is used to get in contact with the customer. We do not keep credit card information on our web sites.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. This site may use cookies to remember a user when the user registers for products or services or to track visits to web pages. If a user does not want to save cookies in the user’s browser, the user may set the browser to reject cookies or to notify the user when a web site tries to place a cookies in the browser. Rejecting cookies does not affect a user’s ability to use the products, features, or services on this site. Cookies are not tied to personally identifiable information.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track popular web pages, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Sharing

We do not share demographic information with others. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SIGMA Assessment Systems is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

## Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your postal code), or if a user no longer desires our services, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. You may email or phone our **Customer Support** to do this. See [our contact information](http://www.sigmaassessmentsystems.com/contact/ "Contact") for addresses.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
